[POLICE OFFICER]
You can count on us. Don't worry.
We will do our best.
You know, that's what you guys always say.
But nothing ever happens.
We won't have any peace
until that Billy leaves us alone!
Look, if you want--
[BEA] Uh, Ma…
What I want
is for you to let me deal with Billy.
I'll handle her, okay?
I can handle her.
[JORDAN] Buddy,
your sister loves you so much.
That's why she did that.
Of course you would side with Billy.
I'm not siding with anyone.
Bro Dude,
didn't you say your father left you too?
If he came back and reached out to you,
wouldn't you want to talk to him?
[DINO] Family is
the Lord's most important gift.
I deeply regret
what I did to my children
and to my wife.
But I believe
that it is not too late.
Amen.
[JORDAN] He just needs time.
Am I wrong?
I mean, we're the same.
I still can't forgive my dad either.
But you love Oliver.
That's all that matters.
[BEA] I hesitated at first, Abi.
I wasn't sure if
it was really Papa I saw in the video.
I went to Billy's house.
He went to see Billy first,
before even coming to his own family.
…listening to our favorite song
during the trip.
What was it again?
- I don't know. You tell me.
- [LAUGHTER]
Who's going to sing it?
- I will! I'm the singer!
- Okay, okay, okay.
- [MARIELA] All right.
- Take the lead. Go!
What are we to him?
Trash?
Trash.
That's all we are to him.
[MARIELA]
Your father has abandoned us.
He has a new family in Manila.
He cheated on me. He cheated on us!
He chose his mistress
and their illegitimate child!
They are to blame for your sister's death!
Damn them. Damn all of them!
Damn them!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's all good now, sir.
Uh, sir…
About the advance pay I was asking for…
Could I please receive it today?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
This is the last time I'll do this, okay?
I'm making a loss because of you!
I'm sorry, sir.
It's just that my mother
still hasn't recovered.
She keeps going back to the hospital.
[MAN SIGHS DEEPLY]
It might be better for your mother
if she just returns to your hometown.
Even if I wanted to,
we have nothing to go back to there.
We already sold our property there
and used that money
to pay for hospital bills.
And where is your father?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN SIGHS]
Okay, I'll get going. Look after the shop.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[YOUNG BILLY GIGGLING]
- You bought a lot, huh?
- Daddy! [GIGGLES]
- [OLIVE] My goodness.
- Pa?
- [OLIVE] She's such a daddy's girl!
- [ENRICO] Are you happy now?
- [YOUNG BILLY] Yes. Thank you, Daddy.
- Pa?
[WOMAN] Oh!
- [ENRICO] Okay, let's go.
- [WOMAN] Watch where you're going.
[OLIVE] Come on, let's hurry up.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Pa?
[OLIVE] Wear your seat belt, dear.
[YOUNG BILLY GIGGLING] Yes.
- [OLIVE] We're so happy.
- [BEA] Pa.
Pa. Pa!
Pa!
Pa.
[BEA SOBBING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[MUSIC TURNS FOREBODING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[APPLAUSE]
…we are preparing something
bigger and better for LoveList.
And I'm sure that here, love is better,
whether it's the first
or second time around,
as long as you are with the right one…
[CROWD] At the right time!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[WOMAN] Yeah!
Congratulations!
Happy anniversary to us, LoveList!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Let's go, let's go!
[BILLY] And because we are celebrating
our second anniversary,
we are preparing something
bigger and better for LoveList.
And I'm sure that here, love is better,
whether it's the first
or second time around
only if you're with the right one.
- At the right time!
- [CHEERS AND CLAPPING IN VIDEO]
- [BILLY] Happy anniversary!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[BILLY] Yay!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES EERIE]
[SPRAY PAINT HISSING, RATTLING]
[VALERIE] Hello, mister?
Hello, mister? Where are you?
I've been waiting for you!
Please hurry up.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES, FADES]
[MOUTHS SILENTLY]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC FADES]
Let's eat.
Oh, where's Oliver?
He's already sleeping.
Then why are there three plates?
Didn't you see my message?
We have a visitor.
- Who?
- [PRECIOUS] Just there.
- Come.
- Ms. Billy! Hello!
Abi!
I went to the center earlier.
I just wanted to thank you
because our conversation
really helped me a lot.
[BILLY] Mm…
But you weren't there,
so Ms. Precious became
the victim of my endless talking.
That's why I brought her with me.
[BILLY] I'm sorry, Auntie Pres.
I'm just mad at people
who can't fight without hiding.
I can't just let them get away with this.
The moment I find out
who started all this,
I'll do everything I can
to put them in jail.
They don't know
what I'm like when I'm angry.
- I'm sorry, Abi.
- [BEA] Hmm?
I'm sorry about this.
I'm not really good at handling my anger.
Oh, Ms. Billy, don't worry about me.
I'm perfectly fine.
If I could,
I'd help you in any way possible.
And I mean, anything.
Enough of that. Come on and eat.
You haven't even taken a bite.
[PRECIOUS] Keep eating, dear.
Come on.
Hey.
Okay.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES,
THEN FADES]
Auntie Pres?
Still nothing?
I already called him.
He's still in his room.
Still refusing to eat.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Auntie, I understand why
he would feel this way.
But I can't give him what he wants.
I'll just bring him food upstairs.
I'll do it.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARIELA] Sweetie! Let's eat!
Coming, Ma!
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[THUDS SOFTLY]
Lunch's ready.
Eat up.
Skipping meals isn't good for you.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
How's your sugar level?
Come on, Oliver.
Eat your meal.
Oliver.
Please eat.
Let me speak to Papa first.
Do you want to be hospitalized again?
Not to mention,
the person you want to talk to
is the one who passed on
that disease to you.
That's not his fault.
You were just a baby when it happened,
so you can't remember it.
But that man you think is kind to you
is the reason our mother died.
Why we almost got separated.
Why we had to live on the streets.
All of that happened
because he abandoned us.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
I don't think I could handle it
if something bad happened to you.
Oliver!
- Are you dizzy?
- Billy.
- Check his sugar level.
- Okay.
[PRECIOUS] Stay there.
[RUSTLING]
Ready?
[CLICKS]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MONITOR BEEPS]
[RUSTLING]
- [CLINKS]
- Have a drink first,
and then eat a lot, okay?
[JUICE TRICKLING]
Go on.
[CLINKS]
Okay.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Grandpa.
I have some good news.
I'm moving you to a better facility.
Somewhere nicer
and bigger.
That's good news, right?
Sir Jordan.
You need to sign a few papers
for the transfer.
- Okay. Grandpa?
- This way, please.
I'll be back, okay?
[DOOR CREAKS]
[DOOR CLICKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Dude.
[JORDAN] Dude?
Oliver's still mad.
- Sir Jordan, your grandpa…
- What's wrong?
He escaped.
But security is already looking for him.
What?!
Jordan?
Are you okay?
Sorry. My grandpa is missing.
What?!
All right, I'm on my way.
- Hurry up.
- Okay, sir.
Why were you being so careless?!
- I'm so sorry.
- This shouldn't be happening.
We're responsible for this.
- I told you--
- Well?
You still haven't found my grandpa?!
Sir, we're very, very sorry.
But we're still looking for him.
We are looking for him, sir.
- I'm sorry.
- Sir, I'll help out too.
No!
Just stay away!
[NURSE] No one's picking up.
Go!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
This shouldn't be happening!
Excuse me.
Have you seen this man?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
All right.
Excuse me.
Can you help me? Ah…
Have you seen him?
- No. I haven't.
- No?
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
All right, thank you.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jordan!
Dude, I can't find him!
Please, I can't lose him too.
Jordan, breathe.
Breathe.
[INHALES, EXHALES SHARPLY]
We'll find him, okay?
Let's split up so we can find him faster.
I'll go this way, you go that way.
Breathe. We'll find him.
Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
My life became worthless.
But everything changed
when I met this girl.
But sadly, I can't be with her.
What do you know?
Your brother is throwing a tantrum,
insisting on going to school.
[BILLY] Auntie, where's Oliver?
Pa?
Why did you leave us?
[BEA] I will avenge us.
I will avenge us both, okay?
[MARIELA] That devil-spawn father of yours
is together with Billy's aunt!
I'll kill them!
I'll kill them both!
- Enrico, let's meet. We need to talk.
- Okay.
People who deceive and steal
deserve to die.
- This is for my daughter!
- Enough, Mariela!
[PRECIOUS] Mariela!
- [MAN] You're a feisty one, I see.
- Mm-hmm. Get it.
[BILLY] Good thing I'm here, right?
What would you do without me?
[JORDAN] We've known
each other for so long.
I can't help
but fall.
So let me take this chance to say,
I think I love you.